<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on blog.woolf.dev</title><link>https://blog.woolf.dev/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on blog.woolf.dev</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.woolf.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notes on the Cube Nuroad Pro FE</title><link>https://blog.woolf.dev/posts/cube-nuroad-race-fe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.woolf.dev/posts/cube-nuroad-race-fe/</guid><description>The Cube Nuroad Race FE provides amazing value for money and is one of the better equipped bikes at the £1,250 price point. However, to be that agressively priced, and be fully equipped (hence FE in the name) with a rack, mudguards, dynamo, and front and rear lights, some corners had to be cut and some compromises made.
This list isn&amp;rsquo;t meant to be a review (though I do love my one) but rather a collection of information I&amp;rsquo;ve come to learn about it over a year&amp;rsquo;s worth of riding, indoors and out, on tarmac and gravel.</description></item><item><title>Viewing Bazel logs using LNAV</title><link>https://blog.woolf.dev/posts/view-bazel-logs-in-lnav/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.woolf.dev/posts/view-bazel-logs-in-lnav/</guid><description>Bazel doesn&amp;rsquo;t support streaming logs to the terminal, which means that long Bazel builds are about as fun as watching paint dry. Fair enough - you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be there babysitting your builds anyway - but sometimes a little more information is nice to see, especially when developing a new rule.
While it&amp;rsquo;s possible to tail -f or less +F the files in bazel-out/_tmp/actions, it can be annoying to deal with output of rules you don&amp;rsquo;t currently care about.</description></item><item><title>Westinghouse ceiling fan remote control with Home Assistant</title><link>https://blog.woolf.dev/posts/ceiling-fan-control/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.woolf.dev/posts/ceiling-fan-control/</guid><description>The Westinghouse Bendan ceiling fan comes with an infrared remote control (model number ID6) which is used to set the fan speed and turn the light on and off.
I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to control the fan speed via my phone for a while, and have managed to do this using Home Assistant and a Broadlink RM3 Mini.
Linking the RM3 Mini to Home assistant Adding the RM3 Mini to Home Assistant was relatively simple - but don&amp;rsquo;t bother with any of the instructions about setting up scripts as it&amp;rsquo;s easier to set the codes manually.</description></item></channel></rss>